papajohnsonline.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Papa John’s Pizza

Effective Date Jan. 1, 2012 (last updated March 1, 2016)

##### This Privacy Policy applies to the sites and apps where it appears.

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where it is located. This includes [www.papajohns.com](https://www.papajohns.com/ "Papa John's Home Page"). It also applies to our mobile sites and apps. By interacting with us on our sites and platforms, you agree to the terms in this Policy.

##### We collect information from and about you.

**We collect contact information.**   
For example, we might collect your name and street address if you register on our site. We might also collect your phone number or email address.

**We collect payment information.**   
For example, we collect your credit card number if you make a purchase.

**We collect information you submit or post.**   
We collect the information you post in a public space on our site. We also collect information when you contact us.

**We collect demographic information.**   
We may collect information like your gender and age. We may also collect your zip or postal code. We might collect this when you contact us or enter a promotion.

**We collect other information.**   
If you use our website, we may collect information about your mobile device, operating system, or web browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. If you use our mobile app, we may collect your GPS location. We might look at how often you use the app and where you downloaded it.

##### We collect information in different ways.

**We collect information directly from you.**   
For example, if you register with us, sign up for our emails or enter a promotion. We also collect information if you contact us. We collect information if you submit orders through our websites or mobile apps.

**We collect information from you passively.**   
We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. To learn more about these tools and how you can control them, [click here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ "Advertising – Privacy & Terms – Google"). We collect information about users over time when you use this website. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. We also collect information from our mobile apps.

**We get information about you from third parties.**   
For example, our business partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you.

**We combine information.**   
For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. Or we may combine information we get from a third party with information we already have.

##### We use information as disclosed and described here.

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions.**   
For example, we might use your information to respond to your customer feedback. We may use your information to contact you about your orders or rewards.

**We use information to improve our products and services.**   
We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us.

**We use information for security purposes.**   
We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.

**We use information for marketing purposes.**   
For example, we might provide you with information about new products, restaurants in your area, and special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps.

**We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.**   
We may contact you about your account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms of Use.

We use information as otherwise permitted by law or as we may notify you.

##### We may share information with third parties.

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.**   
For example, we share information with vendors who send emails for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our websites or run a promotion.

**We will share information with third parties for marketing purposes.**   
For example, we share information with third parties, like corporate affiliates and franchisees, for their marketing purposes.

**We will share information with our business partners.**   
For example, we will share information with third parties who co-sponsor a promotion. These partners may send you information about events and products by mail or email.

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.**   
For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency, investigatory body, or law enforcement requests it. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.**   
For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

##### You have certain choices about how we use your information.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails and/or text messages.**   
To stop receiving our promotional emails or text messages, log in to your account and change your settings or follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions.

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.**   
To learn how to manage how we - and our vendors - use cookies and other tracking tools, please click here.

**You can control tools on your mobile devices.**   
For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone.

##### Your California privacy rights.

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an email to [privacy@papajohns.com](mailto:privacy@papajohns.com "Open your email client to email privacy@papajohns.com"), or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a "Shine the Light" inquiry.

**Consumer Services Team**   
Attention: Privacy Officer   
P.O. Box 99900   
Louisville, Kentucky 40269-0900

##### These sites and apps are not intended for children.

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this Policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request." Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens_educ.html).

##### We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

##### We store information both within and outside the United States.

Information we maintain may be stored both within and outside of the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

##### We may link to other sites or apps or have third party services on our platforms we don’t control.

If you click on a third party link, you will be taken to platforms we do not control. This Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those platforms. Read the other companies’ privacy policies carefully. We are not responsible for these third parties.

Our site may also serve third party content that contains their own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click here. We do not control the use of those technologies.

##### Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy or want to correct or update your information, please email us at [privacy@papajohns.com](mailto:privacy@papajohns.com "Open your email client to email privacy@papajohns.com").

You can also write to us or call at:   
Papa John's International, Inc.   
P.O. Box 99900   
Louisville, Kentucky 40269-0900   

## About Our Ads

##### We use common tracking technologies.

We collect personal information about users over time and across different websites when you use this website or service. We also have third parties that collect personal information this way. To do this, we use several common tracking tools. Our vendors may also use these tools. These may include browser cookies. We may also use web beacons, flash cookies, and similar technologies. 

##### We use tracking technologies for a variety of reasons.

We use tracking tools:

  * To recognize new or past customers.
  * To store your password if you are registered on our site.
  * To improve our website.
  * To serve you with interest-based or targeted advertising (see below for more on interest-based advertising). 
  * To observe your behaviors and browsing activities over time across multiple websites or other platforms. 
  * To better understand the interests of our customers and our website visitors.

##### We engage in interest-based advertising.

We and our partners display interest-based advertising using information gathered about you over time across multiple websites or other platforms. This might include apps.

Interest-based advertising or "online behavioral advertising" includes ads served to you after you leave our website, encouraging you to return. They also include ads we think are relevant based on your shopping habits or online activities. These ads might be served on websites or on apps. They might also be served in emails. We might serve these ads, or third parties may serve ads. They might be about our products or other companies’ products.

##### How do we gather relevant information about you for interest-based advertising?

To decide what is relevant to you, we use information you make available to us when you interact with us, our affiliates, and other third parties. We gather this information using the tracking tools described above. For example, we or our partners might look at your purchases or browsing behaviors. We might look at these activities on our platforms or the platforms of others.

We work with third parties who help gather this information. These third parties might link your name or email address to other information they collect. That might include past purchases made offline or online. Or, it might include online usage information.

##### You can control tracking tools.

Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so depends on the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies. To control flash cookies, which we may use on certain websites from time to time, you can go [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html "Adobe - Flash Player : Settings Manager - Website Storage Settings panel"). Why? Because flash cookies cannot be controlled through your browser settings.

**Our Do Not Track Policy: Some websites have "do not track" features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform. We do not currently respond to those signals.**   
If you block cookies, certain features on our sites may not work. If you block or reject cookies, not all of the tracking described here will stop.

Options you select are browser and device-specific.

##### You can opt-out of online behavioral advertising.

The Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising program provides consumers with the ability to opt-out of having their online behavior recorded and used for advertising purposes. To opt out of having your online behavior collected for advertising purposes, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ "Opt Out From Online Behavioral Advertising By Participating Companies \(BETA\)"). Choices you make are both browser and device-specific.
